Red is 681.
White is 1072.
The final event is the obstacle relay.
Last.
It's Rast.
The current score is 681 for red.
White is 1072.
This obstacle relay is done twice.
Each time, the winner will receive 300 points.
300 points
so there is a chance for an upset.
There is a chance for an upset.
Yes, there is.
Is there a steeplechase? Yes, actually.
Yes.
I've never had a bad memory of it.
I was in middle school, and I had to climb over a net.
I was wearing a pin.
In front of everybody.
I have a bad memory of that.
Today's event was...
Punk-ee.
basketball
Ball scissors
Ping pong ball
Ping pong ball ping-pong ball
spinning ball
Bat
Ping pong ball
And ?
Four scavenger hunts.
Yes, four.
That's four.
It's very important who goes where.
Yes, sir.
We'll all work together to do our best.
We're not going to lose.
We're not going to lose!
Next time's notice
Yes, I'm going to make a decision.
First of all, we have to win the first round.
Bread-eating.
It says "Bread-eating.
That's why I'm confident that I'll be strong for three and a half months.
I'm not weak.
This one
Ah!
It's like this. This is what I've been doing since I turned this thing around.
But this might work for everyone.
Okay, here's the second one.
Okay.
And you can afford it.
With room to spare.
Do it with room to spare.
Let's go shopping!
Let's go shopping.
Bread or no bread?
Shall we go?
I don't think I'm good with bread.
Momochan seems to like Yutaka's pictures.
I'd like to see them.
I thought you looked familiar.
Momochan, this is no good.
Get out.
I just did.
You did?
Yeah.
We should do a bread service or something.
Off shot.
I'm borrowing someone right now.
Sure, I'll just bring him in.
Juice.
What do you want to do on the loan? What do you want to do when you go to the scavenger hunt?
Balls. I can go to all of them.
I can go to any of them.
Ask me anything but borrowing.
The round and round one.
I'll get the gumball.
Hey, let's eat that.
Don't say it.
That's my favorite ping pong game.
Of all the things I'm thinking about.
I'm just, like, behind you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, is it this way?
Now they're gonna be bad at this.
All right.
Pee.
Hey!
Good job!
Two!
One, two, three!
Good job!
Thanks a lot, guys. Thank you for your hard work.
Yay!
This is the last one, everyone.
Wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, Yuuka.
Nice try.
Go, go, go!
Congratulations!
Nice try.
Go, go, go!
Ike ike ike!
Yes!
Ike-ike!
Congratulations!
Go!
Go, go, go!
Congratulations!
Mmm.
Mmm. Ng
род
It's the first time I lost.
Let me try one last time.
Please let me play one last time.
I'll fight fair and square.
Please.
Please!
How many points do I get, by the way?
I'll give you 1,000 points.
Oh, my God!
Are you sure?
I'll really give it to you.
All right.
How long have you been in?
But how many times have you been in there now?
Seven days.
What's it been, like, 300?
1372.
I need 1,000 points to win.
1,200?
1200 and?
Let's give it up.
Let's go head-to-head with the early members of Kilapa.
Let's go for it! Let's go for it.
Here we go. Get ready.
How about that!
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Congratulations!
Dance is the most important thing?
Aaaaah!
Sorry! Sorry!
Aaaaah! Aaaaah!
Aaaaah!
Congratulations!
So, all the events are over!
Thank you very much!
After a few twists and turns, the total score is now 1681 for red
and 1372 for white.
Red wins!
Thank you very much.
Please feel free to beat the red team in the comments section.
I'll take a good look at it, and you can write all about it in the comments section, okay?
I'll like it, won't I?
It's all your hard work.
Congratulations!
For the first time, Girls and Lucky want to collaborate on a field day.
How was it?
It was a lot of fun.
It's not often we get to make such a big difference.
It was great to see you again and talk to you.
Thank you so much.
I was a little drunk at the end.
I was a little bit drunk at the end.
That wasn't the plan, really.
I was supposed to be able to just turn around and go "ah-ha".
The world is spinning faster than I thought it would. The world was already spinning more than I thought it would.
I was the only one who was really drunk the whole time.
Everyone was so kind to me.
The other team's Yohana is my best friend, too.
I'm really worried about her.
The world is distorted, you know.
It's a different world.
And how about Momochan, who discovered a new skill?
She's so sweet.
But I thought it would be easier to get a grip on the bread.
I'm used to that angle of view.
So I didn't have that fear anymore.
I see.
That's great.
I didn't have to worry about anything.
That was amazing.
That was fast.
How was it, Rica?
I got you, but I couldn't get you at all.
I got you.
You did great.
Momoka, you were amazing!
I got you so good!
I got you so good! I got you so good.
It was super cute.
Hold my hand right here.
I'm right here.
It's like this.
It's so cute.
He's so cute.
It was super cute.
I hope everyone enjoyed this different side of me at the field day.
If you want to watch it again, please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
I haven't had the chance to do anything with the other girls, so this was a new experience for me, and it was a lot of fun.
It's something you don't see too often in athletic events.
Yum!
Bread-eating.
I had a lot of fun using the balance ball and eating bread.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
That was my big sister.
Today, I got to meet my cute little sisters.
Yay! Yay!
Thank you!
Actually, I deserved it, but I hadn't eaten breakfast or lunch, and they said I could eat after I finished eating the bread, so I did.
Thank you very much.
I didn't eat bread, though.
It was fun.
What was the most fun?
Eh, I don't know.
Chasing after them.
It was my first time.
Sure, I've done it before.
I'm not doing it. What was that? Did he get away?
The one you put in. That was really difficult.
But it was fun.
I was so nervous at first with all the lucky people.
The tension wasn't low at all.
But it was like this...
But at the end, I said "Minami! I said, "Go!
Go! at the end.
I felt like I had peeled off a little bit of my skin.
I'm glad that I could get closer to everyone.
Everyone had a lot of fun today.
I'm not good at athletic events in general.
I'm not good at sports festivals, but I thought everyone worked really hard and had a good time.
I hope you go to the field day. You want me to go to a field day?
Ah, but it's fun! I like it.
Good for you.
Good job, everybody.
Everyone.
Well, you know, for the white group,
I'm sorry.
But thank you.
I was able to taste the taste of victory.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel!
ласти